No living creatures were harmed
during the filming.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
I told you that I would come for you.
You are in my hand now.
You wanted to keep the beys
away from me.
Who is he to do that, Osman Bey?
So, you are the most capable
commander, huh?
Capable. Very capable!
That's why he depends on
the rogues.
I'll work with the devil even.
Just to destroy the Turks.
Don't worry.
I know that you want to take
Nikea and Bursa.
You know it surely.
But you know that I won't stop too.
Now, you'll tell me the name
of the traitor.
I never liked Nikola.
But we are made of the same material.
Take my head but it won't
make me speak.
Atabey Ahmet. You worked with him.
He was with you.
Let's say, he was.
How will you prove it?
I'm not in a hurry.
Your plots will be revealed.
And so will the traitor.
And you'll lose your head.
But you'll beg me to kill you
sooner then.
Now, tell me the traitor in the tribe...
and receive a swift death.
Selvi...
It's because of me...
I couldn't protect you.
I couldn't.
But I promise you that...
my enduring wife...
the one who took your life...
and the one who was involved
will have no corner to hide.
Firstly, that dog Cebe...
then Osman...
I'll kill them all.
I promise you, Selvi.
I promise you.
My condolences, Barkın Bey.
Thank you.
Women.
I was rude.
Forgive me.
It's my pain.
Otherwise, I know what you
did for Selvi.
Give me your blessing.
It's yours, Barkın Bey.
It happens.
Our pain is fresh.
Our pain is common.
It's yours.
We did all we could but...
we couldn't make it in time.
You have my blessing, Barkın Bey.
My Selvi...
My beautiful sister.
Forgive me, sister.
I couldn't protect you.
Selvi...
Not being afraid of death is
valiant to a point...
now...
let's see if you'll endure
this pain.
Is your endurance enough
for a lit sword.
It's your endurance that
will be tested today, Osman Bey!
Let's talk!
I'm a wolf in the den of a jackal!
Warriors!
We are here, my bey!
Setting an ambush over an ambush?
You need to be smarter to set
a trap here.
This one is the last, my bey.
There are no more scouts.
Thank you.
Now, get all the swords
and bows.
Leave nothing.
Şamil. Turalp.
You'll infiltrate from
the left flank.
Don't make a mistake.
We play an important part.
Yes, my bey.
Alps, we'll infiltrate from the
right flank.
With Osman Bey's plan, this is the
last day of the tyrants.
Come on, put them on.
Yes, my bey.
He traces well!
You can't even see what's in front of
your eyes, Cebe!
I'll rip you into so many pieces that
no one will find you.
You won't die before killing Osman!
Get up!
My bey!
I'll go after him!
Traitor!
The disgrace of the Mongols!
Many called me a traitor.
Now they are all dead.
Are you hitting a man...
or are you forging a weapon?
You are not bad either, Şamil!
Brother, I watch your back!
Me too, brother!
Osman.
Osman, yes.
He ran away from a stone to hit
a rock.
If anyone follows us,
kill them all!
Romanos!
I will kill you!
You can't run away!
Heathens!
I'll kill you first and your
commander later.
We are here, my valiant!
Allah is righteous!
I won't die before seeing
them dead.
I lost whoever I served.
But Rome always takes revenge,
Commander Romanos.
Yes.
But for that, we need to survive first.
So, this is why you
served Romanos.
Yes. Don't you think it's enough?
I had to, to survive.
We lost everything.
If you want to survive.
Then, you'll tell me everything
you know.
And surely, if surviving is
that much important to you.
I'll do anything to live.
Now...
tell me the traitor sending news
to Romanos from our tribe.
I can't say that because they
didn't tell me.
I don't know, Osman Bey.
They never trusted me, Osman Bey!
They didn't say it!
I beg you!
Spare my life!
Let me live!
Let me be your dog.
If I'm a dog, let me serve you!
I beg you, Osman Bey! Let me live!
I beg you!
Let me live, I beg you!
İnegöl Castle
You are better.
You are a murderer!
You killed my atabey!
Stop, shehzad.
You are mad, I know.
You want to destroy.
But stop. Stop and listen.
You are a murderer!
And every word you speak
is a lie!
Why should I listen?
I'll get your head when I'm
saved, Turgut!
Mashallah, you are strong.
But sometimes stopping is better
than acting.
Otherwise, how will you hear
what I say?
Stop!
You should've seen me when I was young.
I would deflect your strike.
But I'm old now.
Come now!
Tie him.
His mouth too.
You are deaf to my words.
You don't hear it.
But you have to hear now.
I'll speak the language you
understand, kid.
I pity your father.
I pity him for having a son like
you to leave his beylig.
Someone who can't
hear or see.
You can only destroy! Solid wrath!
What about justice?
What will you do when your
wrath isn't enough?
I know it's hard for you, but...
to understand what's going on,
you need silence and wits.
But you don't have it.
I didn't kill your atabey.
Surely, I wanted to rip his traitor
head off.
But we make our moves justly.
This is the real greatness.
We are in a big game, son.
I hope it won't be too late for everything
when you see it.
Thank Allah that your father Ali Bey
will learn the truth.
Maybe you'll believe him then.
What are you up to, Barkın Bey?
Bala. You don't look well.
There is something off with you.
Selvi is gone, Aygül.
But she left a mistery behind her.
What are you saying, Bala.
She said something...
What did she say?
I hope it's good.
My condolences, Barkın Bey.
May Allah give you patience.
Selvi is gone now...
She is gone!
Selvi is gone!
Who will control me now?
Who?
My bey.
Even if I burn Kayı Tribe
with its inhabitants...
it won't cool my heart.
I couldn't protect my wife.
You couldn't either, Hüsamettin!
My condolences, my bey.
Hüsamettin.
Those who did this and who caused
this will die!
I will kill them all with my
own hands!
Why are you wriggling, Hüsamettin?
Speak.
-My bey.
-Speak!
Osman Bey caught Cebe.
Come!
Welcome, my bey!
Move!
-Cebe! Cebe!
-My bey!
Killing that dog is my job.
I'll skin him alive!
He'll pay for hurting me!
-Let me go!
-My bey!
What if he speaks?
What if he recognizes you?
My bey, if Osman Bey
finds out...
we'll lose our revenge.
Take him to the caged tent.
Move!
Tell me the situation.
My bey, Selvi Hatun.
She went to heaven.
-My bey.
-Bala.
Aygül.
-Selvi?
-Selvi is a martyr, my bey.
May Allah bless her.
But there is something important
I need to tell you.
Barkın Bey.
Osman Bey.
My condolences.
Thank you, my bey.
I heard that you brought the dog
who killed my wife.
Is it true?
My bey, did you find that dog?
I have. I have.
Osman Bey.
You'll give me my Selvi's, revenge, right?
When the time comes, his blood is yours.
-Don't worry.
-Thank you.
We have that weasel.
I'm relieved.
You should too, Barkın Bey.
My sister will be avenged.
I know that you are in pain.
But the beys will come
to the tent.
You have to come as well.
It is time for revenge, Osman Bey.
I will come.
Yeni Şehir
Open the doors!
Romanos and his army is coming!
May God protect you, Romanos!
-Welcome, Romanos!
-May God protect you, Romanos!
The last unit has arrived.
It seems so.
We have to take care of this as soon as
possible.
-Welcome!
-Welcome, Romanos!
Brave soldiers of Rome!
You have an important reason to be here
today!
Arrogant Turks set their eyes on your
lands!
So you survived, Romanos.
So far, we have lost many lands because
of useless lords!
Now, Osman's new goal is Bursa.
And here is the gate to Bursa!
Yeni Şehir!
We must inform my Bey at once, Father.
-But we...
-We must defeat this dog pack.
...will protect Yeni Şehir!
We won't let the Turks pass!
Because, if we let the Turks pass
through here...
...we will be betraying our history.
Will the mighty soldier of Rome...
...betray Rome?
-He won't! He won't! He won't!
Will the mighty soldier of Rome...
...let the Turks pass?
-He won't! He won't! He won't!
May your sword be sharpened by your
hatred!
We gift the every Turkish head we cut
off...
...to Rome!
-Long live Great Rome!
Beys.
We gathered and discussed.
We set the game and made a plan.
From now on, there is no need for words.
Tomorrow, we will set off and...
...we will besiege Yeni Şehir.
Can I come in, my Bey?
Come in, Turahan.
A messenger came from Çobanoğlu Ali Bey.
Let him in.
-May peace be upon you.
Welcome.
Tell me.
I will.
That's why I came, Osman Bey..
Ali Bey sent me to remind you.
My Bey wants his son Mustafa Bey and
Turgut Bey who is the killed of Atabey.
If you don't give them, you will face
Ali Bey's wrath.
Hey!
Alps!
Stop for a moment.
Our cause is conquest.
But you think about your personal agenda.
So be it.
Turgut Bey accepted giving his life for
this purpose.
But he doesn't want anyone to prevent it.
Thus, Tell Ali Bey that...
...I will deliver Mustafa and Turgut Bey.
How, my Bey?
No. Stop.
-Boran.
-Yes, my Bey.
Accompany the messenger.
As you order, my Bey.
I will gladly forward this, Osman Bey.
You made the right decision, Osman Bey.
We must finalize these matters at once as
there is a conquest to make.
This is what's right.
We sacrificed Turgut Bey for the conquest.
Even though I don't like it...
...it will be.
We will give Turgut Bey and take
Yeni Şehir.
So, what is your move for Yeni Şehir,
my Bey?
I will settle in the Akbıyık district near
Yeni Şehir with my alps.
The others will take the valiants with
them and be with Konur.
When we start the attack, you will come
right after us.
Walk!
Osman Bey!
I was just coming to your tribe to convey
you the news from Ali Bey.
Ali Bey wants his son Mustafa Bey and
Turgut Bey who is the killed of Atabey.
Ali Bey will come with his army if you
don't agree.
I couldn't hear you.
Ali Bey will come with his army if you
don't agree.
I couldn't hear you, messenger.
I am just a messenger, Osman Bey.
Messenger, I will listen to you when you
come to my gathering.
What do you mean, Osman Bey?
Ali Bey doesn't see the truth. A game
is being played.
They are covering the truth.
But I will uncover that truth.
You will do as I say for this purpose.
You will give your statement on front of
everyone as I say.
Alps, take care of the messenger.
No harm will come to him.
Come on.
How will Osman Bey manage this matter?
You will know it when there is something
you need to know.
You will be our guest for now.
What does this mean?
I did everything you told me to.
It is Osman Bey's order.
Earning his trust isn't easy
You are already on bad terms with Ali Bey.
You are still trying him.
This is disrespect!
The real disrespect is to judge
without knowing the truth.
Osman Bey doesn't trust Ali Bey, who is
infuriated and his messenger at all.
Alps! Take our guests to the tent!
Give them anything they need.
The price for this will be heavy.
The burden of the eye that does
not see the truth is heavy.
Whoever is blind, let them pay for it,
messenger!
Come on.
So Barkın is a traitor?
How, Bala?
I know we aren't that close but we haven't
seen any evil from him all these years.
If he was the enemy enough to betray us,
wouldn't we have seen it until today?
You say so but Atabey Ahmet Bey was
Barkın's friend.
He didn't say anything when they came.
He didn't say anything when Atabey
died.
Why did he keep silent all those times?
What about Selvi?
Selvi wouldn't do this to us even Barkın
had done, Bala.
She wouldn't.
She maybe didn't even know.
But Osman was suspecting Atabey Ahmet.
Also, you and me both know that Turgut
Bey wouldn't kill him.
Right.
But then who did? You said Barkın was
his friend.
Selvi told Barkın that Turgut Bey
was going to İnegöl.
Selvi did?
So she was a spy?
How could this have happened?
She was my sister.
She didn't do it on purpose, I suppose.
She was very upset.
Then, they learned the place of the ambush
from Barkın.
Later, they killed Ahmet and blamed it on
Turgut Bey.
Hence, Ali Bey, who was Osman Bey's
friend, became his enemy.
They want to isolate us.
For all these years we have fed enemies,
not friends.
We've seen many traitors, Malhun. All of
them were unbelievable.
What about Selvi? Did she know her husband
was a traitor?
I don't think so.
She wouldn't lie on her deathbed.
She said what she had to and left.
She thinks that her husband works for the
sake of the tribe.
Oh, my beautiful sister!
Who knows what he did behind us
all these years.
Oh, my unfortunate sister!
Let's go to Osman Bey at once. I couldn't
tell him yet.
Let's go so that the traitor will be
punished as soon as possible.
-Can I come in?
-Come in, my Bey!
My Bey, we were coming to you.
Tell me.
My Bey, Selvi gave us crucial information.
Don't worry, we won't stay here for long.
You worked with Osman Bey while you could
just give Ali Bey's message.
You know nothing!
I had to. I didn't do it willingly.
Know this!
I shouldn't have trusted you, Osman Bey.
I shouldn't have believed you.
So you say Barkın is the traitor.
Selvi confessed.
She told Barkın that Turgut Bey
was leaving.
Obviously, Barkın sent the news to his
close friend Ahmet Bey.
So...
...what else did Selvi Hatun say?
She said that Barkın did all of this for
his tribe.
And not to misunderstand him.
But she was so uneasy.
She kept asking for our blessings.
Since she feels this guilty...
...he's done huge mistakes.
My Bey.
Can Barkın be involved in the game set
against Turgut Bey.
If he was, he must have hidden well.
Selvi Hatun said he was friends with
Ahmet Bey.
Did he kill his own friend?
Is what Selvi Hatun said evidence of
Barkın Bey's treachery?
He's been with us all these years.
He didn't make a mistake as well.
Why would he betray us now?
Since he's done all these while looking
into our eyes...
...he is capable of killing Ahmet.
He is.
A traitor doesn't need a reason.
He must have a benefit.
We will find all out.
We will plan the game on Barkın.
Aktemur.
You will go to Ali Bey with Baysungur.
Konur.
You will take Mustafa and Turgut Bey.
As for you, Cerkutay...
...you will go after Hüsamettin and
Barkın.
Keep your eyes on him.
He will go to the funeral.
If he is a traitor...
...he will definitely send some news.
As you order, my Bey.
My Bey.
The messenger is still captive.
What about them?
We will keep them.
We will keep him until our plan works.
As you order, my Bey.
Here you go.
Forgive me, my Bey.
I got this traitor in the tribe.
No, Malhun. You have no fault.
They are hypocrites.
They didn't deceive only you...
...but all of us.
Don't be hard on yourself.
Now we are going to fulfill our last duty
to Selvi Hatun.
Come on.
The lord and Romanos are cautious.
The number of soldiers increases
day by day.
I found out today...
...that healer women and nuns are
coming from İznik.
They take precautions just in case.
Healers and nuns...
This is very important information.
We will convey this to Osman Bey
at once.
Immediately.
-I am sorry for your loss, Barkın Bey.
-Thank you.
-I am sorry for your loss.
-Thanks.
-I am sorry for your loss, Barkın Bey.
-Thank you.
Hüsamettin.
Yes, my Bey?
Go to Romanos.
Tell him that...
...Osman will attack Yeni Şehir.
He will settle in Akbıyık...
...with his closest alps.
Tell him to...
...kill Osman this time.
Tell him that...
...if he can't manage to kill Osman
again...
...Barkın Bey won't leave him to Osman.
He will kill you himself.
As you order, my Bey.
Let's see what you are up to.
Barkın Bey and...
...his dog.
What took you from me...
...wasn't the disease, my Selvi.
It was the Kayı tribe.
I will kill them all.
Osman.
Kayıs.
And even that useless Romanos.
I will take your revenge, my Selvi.
I promise you.
I promise you that...
...I won't let any of them live.
I will kill Osman.
And his hatuns.
And his children.
I promise you, Selvi.
I will kill them all.
My baby.
Mother.
Father.
My aunt Selvi won't return.
Oh, my angel daughter.
Make them forge my sword now, father.
I will take my aunt Selvi's revenge!
Come here. Come here.
Come here.
Son, bring it.
My angel.
Give it to me.
Let me see it first.
Good.
Son.
Praise be! It is exactly what I wanted.
Since you forged it...
...you will give it.
We forged it together with your brother
Alaaddin, sister. It is yours.
Thank you, brother.
It suits you.
Come on.
Kiss your brother's hand.
My beautiful girl. Be careful. All right?
Draw your sword only at the enemy.
Also, don't hold it and hurt yourself
before the training.
You kept your promise, father.
You must keep your promise as well,
my beautiful.
Be a good sister to your brother.
No jeaolusy.
Come here.
Come here, my Orhan.
Come here, my Malhun.
Osman Bey...
...the soil on earth and the Great Tengri
in heaven are my witness that...
...I am regretful.
I only wanted gold.
Don't you see my state?
I am begging you!
In the presence of Great Tengri, my wish
is that you forgive me, Osman Bey.
A hungry man doesn't care who he works
for.
You stay here still like a dog but...
...whenever you open your mouth, dirt
comes out of your mouth.
Dog barks louder when trapped.
You are trapped as well.
But let me tell you something.
Your words mean nothing from now on.
Back then, you added a Mongol
to your alps.
I heard many times that
you fight as a Turk.
As you trusted him.
As you took him.
Spare me too, Osman Bey.
You'll have another sword
serving you.
Do you know the pharoah?
When he denied Hz. Moses...
when he realised that he'll get drowned,
he said that he believed.
But his faith wasn't real.
Yours is just like the pharoah.
So, don't expect any mercy
from me.
You surrounded when you had
nowhere to run.
Our followers' swords should
shine with light of faith.
May I enter, my bey?
Barkın Bey is here.
Come.
My bey, Osman Bey's nephew Aktemur
is here.
He has news.
Aktemur! Murderer of my son!
You! You killed me son!
Kill him!
I didn't kill your son!
Your son is alive!
I brought you news from Osman Bey.
I came here as an envoy.
My life is under your protection.
Where is my envoy, Aktemur?
If he is alive, where is my son?
Osman Bey is hosting him because
he is tired.
They'll come with my bey.
If Osman makes another mistake...
if he hurts my envoy...
We said that your envoy is
our guest.
They are treating him the best way.
And we are hoping that you'll
do the same.
Ali Bey, your son was impudent again.
And Aktemur Bey gave him a lesson.
But don't worry. He is alive.
I didn't give you a lesson when you
were impudent.
Now be silent!
Let the envoy speak.
What does Osman Bey say?
He wanted you to know that he'll
bring Turgut Bey personally tomorrow.
Your son will be there too,
safe and sound.
Osman Bey will serve justice.
I was thinking that the Kayı learned
nothing from their ancestors.
But Osman is coming round.
The Kayı stood with justice yesterday
as they'll tomorrow.
The Kayı never changed, Ali Bey.
But you are blinded to the truth when it
doesn't match with your profits.
But don't worry. Justice of the Kayı
will open all the blind eyes.
Take our guest to his room.
Did this man kill my Selvi?
He did.
Washing this dog in blood is
your right.
You took Selvi from me.
Forgive me.
Show mercy!
No mercy.
You took Selvi from me...
and I took your life.
İnegöl Castle
I came to take Mustafa.
It's the end of your visit, shehzad.
Turgut!
If you be impudent,
I'll take your life!
Turgut Bey, you need to come
with us too.
We'll give you to Ali Bey.
It's Osman Bey's order.
What happened, Turgut Bey?
You were speaking highly.
Now you got what you deserve.
But your bey understood
what you are made of.
He understood and sold you.
I wish you knew what I'll do to
you.
I know myself, Konur.
I won't surrender for something
I didn't do!
And not because of this boy's
slander.
But my Osman brother's order
will be followed.
Who are you to get listened, Turgut?
Osman Bey tells you to come and you come.
He tells you to go and you go.
When the truth gets revealed...
we'll see what water can
wash your dirt.
Don't give me advice, Turgut.
What do you know?
You killed an innocent!
Traitor! Murderer!
Turgut Bey.
Osman Bey expects you both
safe and sound.
Both Gündoğan and I will come, Konur.
Both of us.
YENİ ŞEHİR
So, tell me.
What news have you
brought from Barkın Bey?
He is going to deliver Osman Turgut.
Because of Turgut, Kayıs and
Chobanids almost got into a fight.
Osman took that opportunity
away from us.
He is going to destroy our entire plan...
...by giving away his most trusted man...
...at the expense of destroying
our reputation.
After delivering Turgut...
...he'll attack Yeni Şehir.
Osman.
Osman. Osman.
If Osman delivers Turgut...
...Beys won't have any
trust for him no more.
They'll think they'll be let
down at the first opportunity.
Does he still want to
fight on these terms?
Let him come.
What are the battle plans?
The condition of the soldiers?
Osman will arrive at
Akbih spot with his alps.
Barıkın Bey says it's a proper
location for an ambush.
He says they should strike
before they settle in well.
Beys will come from behind.
When Osman dies they won't matter.
Good.
Then, be ready.
I'm going to set the
cruelest trap for him.
Osman thinks he's coming
to expand his lands.
But I'll burn him...
...and mix his ashes with
the lands he's trying to take.
Barkın Bey also says...
...this is the last chance for Romanos.
If he can't manage to
kill Osman once again...
...I'll kill Romanos myself.
Then, you tell your Bey...
...that Akbıyık will become Osman's grave.
Enjoy it, my valiant.
May Allah bless you!
I followed Barkın's man.
He brought me all the way here.
That reprobate.
It seems...
...that he'll send word to that
Romanos scoundrel, Hüsamettin.
What are you saying, Davut Usta?
Romanos was here.
He'll be the commander
in chief of the army.
Damn dogs!
They're getting prepared.
They also brought herbalists
and nuns from İznik.
I should go and inform
my Bey about all of this.
Thank you both!
But, I won't leave that
Hüsamettin dog alone.
Thank you!
Cerkutay, may Allah help you!
May he protect you!
Thank you!
You put your lives in danger
on enemy soil for war.
May Allah bless you!
May...
May Allah help us!
I should go.
Let's go. Let's go.
Are you better now, even just a bit?
The death of Selvi...
...will keep hurting me
for the rest of my life.
But...
...knowing that...
...that dog is dead...
...comforts me, Osman Bey.
But, I haven't gotten what I wanted.
There is a traitor amongst the
beys that are in my command.
And collaborates with Cebe.
If so...
...why did you make me kill that dog?
We could have made him speak, my Bey.
Do you put your tribe in
danger to comfort me?
Maybe,...
...I didn't feel the need to.
Or,...
...the death of that dog gave me
more than enough information.
Good then.
If you know who he is, you can punish him.
Neither Kayı nor Kızılbey Oğulları
will suffer this kind of pain again.
But, tell me Osman Bey...
...does that dog have anything
to do with the death of Selvi?
Is he the only one?
I'll ask.
I'll ask all of it.
Don't worry at all.
Now that Cebe is dead...
...someone else will talk.
Who is that traitor?
Romanos and Cebe.
They all work for the same person.
Now that Cebe is dead...
...Romanos will speak.
By the way...
...the enemies outside...
...and the traitor inside...
...will not be able to prevent
the conquests, Barkın Bey.
We're going to take Yeni Şehir.
Mother, when is he going to kick?
There is more time for that, son.
He's too little.
You ask like you don't know.
What? You seem excited.
I know but I can't wait, mother.
I want him to come out and
grow up quickly if Allah permits.
If Allah permits, Alaaddin.
If Allah permits.
Uncle Gündüz will also have a baby...
...I get upset.
But he'll be our brother as well.
I'll tell him the heroic
deeds of my uncle.
That's right.
It is a test, Alaaddin.
Your sheik grandfather
probably has told you.
Everybody has a different test.
My good-hearted brave son.
So, tell me...
...how is the training going?
Do you want to have weapons
training with your mother?
I don't have the ability yet to
draw on Bala Hatun, mother.
I know my place.
- My Osman.
- Alaaddin.
Alaaddin.
Come.
My smart boy.
He knows very well that drawing
on Bala Hatun is not that easy.
But,...
...her eyes are sharper
than any weapon, son.
You look tired, my Bey.
No.
Whenever I stroke the hair of my
kids and look into their eyes...
...tiredness goes away.
Alaaddin,...
...- you'll have another brother, son.
- That's right, father.
I can't wait.
The time isn't passing for me.
Same with me.
It's not passing.
All of my children give me
a different excitement.
But, I...
...love all of you.
Make sure you also love and
protect each other as well.
My brothers are in my hands, father.
Praise be!
Come.
You come too.
Mother.
Aunt Ayşe.
Aren't you pregnant?
What are you doing in battle?
Don't be afraid, son. We
have a different task.
Alaaddin,...
...do you know how many times your mother
fought when she had you in her belly?
That's where your skills come from.
You started learning
in your mother's belly.
It's not that big of a
battle, don't worry.
I'll go with Bacıyans and
protect your mother.
She'll come back safe if Allah permits.
If Allah permits.
Praise be, hatuns!
You're already prepared.
Bala, Ayşe, it would be
beneficial to be careful.
You say that to them but
your arm is wounded, mother.
Don't you worry.
Boys, you may be baffled and think...
...why are they going
to battle in this state?
Mothers get tired.
They get hurt, but they don't give up.
For what?
So that you could wake
up to a better morning.
Now, your job is to stay
here and pray for us.
Isn't that right?
That's right. Pray.
Pray so that we could come back safely.
Come on, I'm ready!
What are we waiting for?
It's the order of Osman Bey.
Let's not wait.
My beautiful daughter,
didn't we talk about this?
You're too litte.
When it's time, aunt Bala
will have you join Bacıyans.
But not now.
Then, I'll go.
You go, we'll pray for you.
Right, sister?
Before a battle, the kids should
pray for their mothers and fathers.
You are right my big brothers.
Let's pray so that they
can come back safely.
He met with Romanos in Yeni Şehir.
You said whoever works
with him is the traitor.
- We'll find him if Allah permits, my bey.
- If Allah permits.
He may be up to something
behind Barkın's back, my bey.
We should be sure.
We'll learn. We'll learn, Cerkutay.
You go to Bala, now.
The Osman who doesn't
know his place is here.
My father will cut your head
off after Turgut, as well.
You went too far.
Why did you rush?
You don't have to hit me for
me to cut your head off, Konur.
You wait for your turn.
We say we want to go forward...
...your ancestor comes
and stands behind us.
That dog Ata Bey with you...
...collaborates with the enemy.
Just so Ali Bey doesn't stand behind us.
Of course, he will. He
is the enemy after all.
That's his nature.
But you know what's bad?
Adding fuel to the flame.
Forgetting your cause for
your own self-interest.
You work with the devil without knowing
what you're doing and aiding the enemy.
It's good that there aren't
many of you among Turkmen.
Turkmens always side with us.
They get heartened by our victory
and be proud of our conquest.
But, thank goodness that
Ali Bey thinks that way as well.
He's just being played.
Alps, on your horses.
Aktemur.
I like and respect your
ancestor and your uncle.
But if they try to play me...
...the first head to be cut
off is yours, know that.
My Bey, they're coming!
Ali Bey.
Osman Bey.
Come on, deliver my son and Turgut Bey.
Be patient.
YENİ ŞEHİR
The army is ready, let's get on the road.
Commander Romanos is
waiting, be quick, blacksmith.
Blacksmith.
I'll nail those horseshoes
on your skull! Be quick!
Will this army be able to stop the Tuks?
Yeni Şehir doesn't even have walls.
Yeni Şehir may not have walls.
But with the trap, I'll set up for them,
Osman won't even be able to come close...
...to the city.
Ali Bey.
I told you there was something
going on with this job.
I told you not to lose
control of your anger.
I told you to wake up from
the sleep of heedlessness.
But, I will awake you from
The Ata Bey Ahmet who
disguised as one of my alps.
He collaborated with the Mongols.
That's why he was the one who
attacked Mustafa with Turgut Bey.
But there are two more people.
One of them is Romanos, the other is Cebe.
Cebe is on the ground right now.
Romanos doesn't have much time either.
Let's get to the main point.
Ata Bey Ahmet was also
in collaboration with them.
But, what they were
doing caused his demise.
What are you talking about, Osman Bey?
Ali Bey, they're doing all of this
just so you don't side with us.
They wish to prevent the conquests.
They wish to weaken Kayı.
That's why...
...they set up Turgut Bey.
But there is one other person
who's also involved in this.
About him...
...he...
...he is Barkın.
Come here, come here, you
black sheep of Turkmen!
What is wrong, Osman?
Are you going to slander me to
get yourself out of this situation?
Are you going to burn me
in order to save Turgut?
Shut up!
You won't speak unless I tell you to!
Ali Bey,...
...you're going to tell everything.
Start talking.
- Boran!
- I'm on it, my Bey.
Hüsamettin!
Where are wandering off to like a
cowardly dog trying to escape his fate?
Run, Hüsamettin, run.
It's been a while since
I hunted a traitor.
There you go.
Run, traitor.
Run.
- Baysungur.
- My bey?
Bring him.
This Barkın...
...didn't even shy away from
sacrificing his partner Ahmet....
...for his moves.
And from making his
wife Selvi a spy against us.
Mustafa,...
...tell me...
...who told you the
location of Turgut Bey?
Mustafa!
Tell us!
Barkın Bey did.
Barkın's friendship
with Ahmet is apparent.
And it's obvious that he
is a part of this scheme.
Now admit it yourself.
Admit what, Osman? What?
I've never been part of
a treacherous act, but...
...I'll make you pay for this.
I am not a traitor!
Shut up!
You're not a traitor?
Hüsamettin.
Boran.
Boran, you will die!
Attacks helplessly when
backed into a corner.
Come here.
You don't have the heart, Boran.
Killing an unarmed man
would suit a coward like you.
Come here.
Come.
You traitor!
Stop!
Leave me be and
I'll tell you everthing.
Of course, you will.
But you will tell everything in
front of Ali Bey and Osman Bey.
Come.
Walk! Come on!
Enough!
Osman Bey.
You talk about justice...
...but slap someone without any evidence.
Ali Bey,...
...you don't believe me, huh?
I see someone who did everything
he could to give Turgut Bey away.
Where is betrayal in that?
The rest is superfluous.
Superfluous?
Come here.
So...
....come here.
If...
...the head is not going to talk...
...then the feet will.
Speak!
Barkın was the student of Arius.
Shut up!
He is lying to save his own skin!
They set up everything together.
I have no involvement, my Bey.
I just follow orders.
Bey told me to do it, so I did it.
Spare me.
Forgive me.
Keep going.
They blew up Söğüt together.
Then Umur Bey, and
Ivaz Bey killed all of them.
Send word to Nikola, Arius...
...Romanos one by one.
I told you everything you wanted, my bey.
Spare my life, I beg of you, my bey!
Ali Bey,...
...you're rushing again.
You got things to hear.
You got things to see.
Wait for a bit.
There.
You see?
Do you know who has the same thing?
Alps!
Bring him.
Ali Bey.
Ata Bey.
Come here.
Do you see it?
That is the evidence of
Ahmet being one of them.
How could Ahmet...
You tricked me.
You made me a part of your treachery.
Murderers!
Murderers! Murderers!
You killed Umur Bey.
You killed your father-in-law Ivaz Bey.
You worked with Romanos and Nikola.
Tell me! Tell me!
For what?
People like you...
...only want the power for themselves.
Beys, noblesses....
...nobles...
...the ones who take posts
from their fathers....
...ones on the throne...
...I held on to this life
with my paws, Osman.
Humans are born alone...
...die alone.
I lived alone.
Now, you may ask: "why?"
I'll tell you why.
For power.
To be acknowledged.
I was dropped on the sea...
...and hugged Arius.
This power is poisonous, Osman.
I became a Bey and it wasn't enough.
Everyone close to me is a threat to me.
I made a deal with the
devil to destroy you.
I killed Umur.
And I killed Ivaz as well.
Also, the one from my
blood Ahmet, I killed him too.
Ali Bey.
You were looking for the killer.
The ones I killed are
waiting for me, Osman.
Come on.
But I'm happy that
I'll reunite with Selvi.
Come on!
Scoundrels like you don't
deserve a righteous love.
How could you look at the face
of the Hatun you killed the father of?
Shame on the ones who sell
their soul and honor for power.
You came without blood,
you'll leave without blood.
Your revenge is taken, Mari.
In the name of Allah the merciful.
Alaaddin.
My prince.
What is it that's making you sad? Tell me.
I can't, my sheik grandfather.
I'm embarrassed.
Why, is it a bad thing?
I look at my father...
...he cries on his prayer rug every night.
Isn't that right brother, you see it too.
In dawning time and after isha prayer
he cries on his prayer rug reading Quran.
Every day, every night.
I asked him once, my sheik grandfather.
I asked: "Why are you crying?"
''Because of love'' he said.
He was crying for his love for Allah
and the prophet.
So, how is this bad, shehzad?
The bad is not on my father
but on me.
I can't cry.
Don't I love our Allah and prophet?
I don't know how to increase my love.
Firstly, know this, children.
Not everyone is created
the same way.
Some leak their love out
of their eyes.
Some give life to a flower, a tree
with their love...
or mercy to humans.
Thank Allah, your father does
both of them.
But don't be sad for not crying.
Even being sad about this shows
how big your love is.
You already love but...
you ask how you can love Allah
and the prophet more!
The way to that is Marifetullah.
What is Marifetullah,
my sheik grandfather?
Marifetullah is science.
Science of knowing Allah.
Loving comes after knowing.
To know Allah, you should know the
prophets and Qur-an.
Whatever your tongue speaks of,
takes place in your heart.
For that reason, we praise Allah
five times a day.
Hz.Muhammad, peace be upon his name,
we say...
we speak his name and send regards
to him.
This increases our love.
The other thing that will
increase our love is...
learning Prophet Muhammad's sayings.
What do we say when
we learn it?
We see how the prophet lived.
Loving Allah and the prophet is living
Islam and spreading it.
As sincere and strong
our efforts are...
our love will increase.
May your love last forever.
Amin, my sheik grandfather.
Amin.
The horsemen are coming!
My beautiful wife.
Allah bless your hands.
You are still hungry. Here.
Take it.
My valiant husband.
Eat quickly.
We have a job to do.
You speak so smoothly lately.
Aren't you mad at me?
I'm not, Cerkutay.
Allah Allah!
Our Mother Selcan's efforts
worked!
Thank Allah!
If you don't want smooth...
I can be harsh too, Cerkutay.
Thank you, my wife.
You are the crown of my head.
Cerkutay.
If someday...
something happens to me...
and I die before you...
-What are you saying, Aygül?
What are you saying, mad girl?
Allah forbid.
Of course, Cerkutay.
But if...
something like that happens...
our children are yours to protect.
Don't let them miss me.
Don't say that, Aygül!
Don't say that, mad girl!
I know you.
Whenever someone dies,
you are like this.
Death is real, Cerkutay.
They are coming.
Come on, Cerkutay.
If death will come...
it should come to me first.
Come on.
Let's inform them.
They are coming.
Be ready.
Sisters! Be ready!
Thank you, Osman Bey.
As you said then, you woke us up
from our sleep of negligence.
Thank you. Thank you.
Kayı's banner will stay in the shadow of
justice to those who want battle.
Those who have the courage for
their hearts should come with us.
Thank you.
Come on!
Come on, mad girl!
Come on, sisters!
Come on!
Don't be afraid.
We won't hurt you.
We won't harm you. We just
want your clothes.
You'll wear those.
And we'll wear your
clothes.
I hope you won't resist.
Don't be afraid. We'll host you in a
safe place until we are done.
Women.
Go and change your clothes
over there.
Come on.
Alps.
Go to Osman Bey.
Tell him that it's going as planned.
At the end of the street.
I saw him with Osman,
Commander Romanos.
He was in a disguise...
but I know that it's the same person.
Call a support unit!
Right away, sir.
I won't leave here before
finding them.
They are galloping toward us.
But they'll get hit by the
Roman spears!
It's been a long time, Konur...
...Alp.
It's true, Uğurlu.
Seeing you like this broke
my heart, Konur.
When I left you, you were
with the vizier.
Now, you are an alp of
a Turkmen bey.
And I'm the envoy of the Seljuks
in their palace.
It's an honor to stand behind
Osman Bey who follows justice.
It's the cause that I
believe in, Uğurlu.
But you only believe in the palace.
Welcome, brother Balaban.
Thank you, brother.
-I came--
-We don't have much time now.
You took a long way.
Let's go to the tribe.
Osman Bey is waiting.
Alps!
In the name of God, the infinitely
Compassionate and Merciful.
Praise be to God, Lord of all the worlds.
The Compassionate, the Merciful. Ruler...
Come on, we need to go!
Come on!
What's the situation?
Say it first, smith!
There is no time, Kumral!
Come on!
Turn into a priest and lest run
before Romanos' dogs come.
Go to every street!
Search every house!
It's too late now!
The soldiers are coming!
Well, Kumral.
It's time to fight shoulder
to shoulder, huh?
We've seen this day too.
We'll leave this street by killing
them one by one.
Probably, you will all die!
And even me!
Why is the happiness?
Martyrs aren't dead, Priest Hristo.
Martyrs are always alive.
-Allah is eternal!
-Allah is righteous!
Open every door!
Search every house!
Beys!
Before the conquest, we solved
every issue!
Thank Allah.
-Boran.
-My bey.
Here! Here is Umur Bey and İhvaz Bey's
murderer!
And the head of many other
evil!
Treacherous Barkın!
We made him pay!
Now we found the traitors!
Now, whoever holds his leashes,
we'll go after them!
If anyone has an issue, he should say it.
If you don't have an issue.
Then, it's time we turn our
face to the West!
Our alps barely hold their
weapons on their sheaths.
I see that alps are ready for battle!
We are ready, my bey!
Then, we'll turn our horses
to the West!
I pity those who'll stand
in our way.
It's time.
Let him come.
My bey, the envoy brought news
from Sultan Alahaddin.
Speak.
Osman Bey, my words belong to Seljuk
sultan Alahaddin.
My words are his words.
The bey of Kayı, protector
of the borders, Osman Bey.
I hear that you forget that you are my
shadow. You act on your own.
Your ears are deaf to my words.
Your tongue knows no respect.
Now, you want to take Yenişehir.
I don't allow it.
If my words are ignored again...
The army marching from Konya will
crush you.
This will be my last word to you.
I heard Sultan Alahaddin's words.
But...
but I won't send a messenger.
You'll personally convey
my words to Sultan Alahaddin.
Kayı Tribe isn't anyone's shadow!
Is there are free country in Konya
that we can be the shadow of?
The Kayı, Kızılbeyoğlu,
and all the tribes on the borders...
they are all under my rule!
Now, tell Sultan Alahaddin.
I'm going to take Yenişehir.
And when I return, I'll have khutbah
read in my name in İnegöl!
And I'll have my own coins.
Whoever holds the banner
on the borders...
holds the rule!
O' people!
We'll put Islam's flag
in Yenişehir!
And Yenişehir will be our home!
And at the same time, for Bursa and
İznik's conquest, it'll be our quarters.
Rome's winds are harsh on us.
But those who can't stand against
those winds are destined to fly away!
If we can't stand tall gainst
that wind...
then we'll be removed from these lands.
For that reason!
O' the people!
O' the warriors of Kayı!
For the world's order...
for Allah's words!
Our target is Yenişehir!
Allahu Akbar!
Allahu Akbar! Allahu Akbar!
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com